Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Periodicals and Publications, 1955-2007
  - Small Press Publications, 1955-2006
    - Black Power, Achievement, Thought, 1960-2006
      - Goddesses of the World, 1994; Askhew, Carol "Abi" (Box 467, Folder 2)
      - The Green Book, Undated; Qathafi, Muammar Al (Box 467, Folder 3)
      - The History of Islam and Black Nationalism in the Americas, 1985; Rashad, Adib (James Miller) (Box 467, Folder 4)
      - The History of Islam and Black Nationalism in the Americas, 1985-1991; Rashad, Adib (Box 467, Folder 5)
      - History of the Nation of Islam, 1993-1995; Muhammad, Elijah (Box 467, Folder 6)
      - The Honorable Louis Farrakhan: A Minister for Progress, 1985 (Box 467, Folder 7)
      - How the Bible and DollarBill are a Great 555-666-777, 2000-2003; Epps, S. (Box 467, Folder 8)
      - How the Bible and DollarBill are a Great 555-666-778, 2000-2003; Epps, S. (Box 467, Folder 8)
      - I Used to Love H.I.M., Undated; Merat, Khepper-a (Box 467, Folder 9)
      - The Journal of the Moorish Paradigm, Book 12, 1993-2005; Bey, Hakim (Box 467, Folder 10)
      - The Journal of the Moorist Paradigm Vol. 1, Issue 1, 2001-01; Northgate Civilization (Box 464, Folder 5)
      - Kemeticism: The World Religion for Black Peoples, 1995; Odak, Osaga (Box 467, Folder 11)
      - King Alfred Plan, Undated; Miles, Zears L. (Box 464, Folder 1)
      - The King Alfred Plan: The Plan for Extermination of the Black Race in the United States of America, Undated (Box 464, Folder 2)
      - Look Up, You Mighty Race!, Undated; Garvey, Marcus (Box 464, Folder 3)
      - Making Impressions, 2005-03; America/Typecast (Box 512, Folder 11)
      - Melanin: The Chemical Key to Black Greatness, Vol. 1, Undated; Barnes, Carol (Box 464, Folder 4)
      - Moors Battle in Court; 40 Hurt, Undated (Box 464, Folder 7)
      - Moors Order of the Roundtable: Civic Lesson Book No. 14, 1996; Bey, Taj Tarik; Moorish American Heritage Series (Box 464, Folder 6)
        Camden, New Jersey
      - Mr. Muhammad Speaks Vol. 1, No. 1, 1960-05 (Box 464, Folder 8)
        New York
      - New African No. 419, 2003-06 (Box 464, Folder 9)
      - The Origin of Rap Music, 1994; McClendon, Robert Jr. James (Box 512, Folder 12)
      - Pandora's Box: The Ultimate "Unseen Hand" Behind the New World Order, 1993; Christopher, Alex (Box 464)
      - Philadelphia Uncovered, 2006; International Indigenous Society (Box 512, Folder 13)
      - Protocols of the Meetings of the Learned Elders of Zion, 2003-09-19; Mardsen, Victor (Box 464, Folder 10)
      - Putnam News Edition 7, Vol. 2, 2000-09 (Box 464, Folder 11)
      - Race Traitor, 1997 (Box 465, Folder 1)
      - Rap, Hip Hop, and the New World Order: The Research Edition Volume 1 Bibliography, 1997; Awadu, Keidi Obi (Box 486, Folder 26)
      - The S.G.B.P.: The "Realistic" Word, 1990-12; Crown Panther (Box 467, Folder 12)
      - The Science of Rap, 1996; KRS-One (Box 512, Folder 14)
      - The Suppressed Rebellion, 2002; ed. Shabazz, Areeb Malik (Box 465, Folder 3)
      - Supreme Lessons of the Gods and Earths, 1993 (Box 466, Folder 20)
      - The Supreme Wisdom Vol. 2, Undated; Muhammad, Elijah (Box 467, Folder 14)
      - The Supreme Wisdom: Solution to the So-Called Negroes' Problem, Undated; Muhammad, Elijah (Box 467, Folder 13)
      - Tips on Quick and Easy Ways Afrikans Can Commit Subtle Suicide, 1987-08; Kambon, Kamau (Box 465, Folder 4)
      - The Trojan Horse Analysis, 1993-1996; Awadu, Keidi Obi (Box 465, Folder 5)
      - United African Movement Presents H. Khalif Khalifah and Independent Black Writers, 2001-08-29 (Box 466, Folder 19)
      - The United Independent Compensatory Code/System/Concept, 1971; Fuller, Neely Jr. (Box 465, Folder 6)
      - The United States of Hip-Hop, 1992; Shabazz, Julian L.D. (Box 512, Folder 15)
      - Visions for Black Men, 1991; Akbar, Na'im (Box 467, Folder 15)
      - Wake Up America; Destruction of the Trade Centers: Occult Symbolism Indicates Enemies within Our Own Government, 2002-02-05; Howard, Robert (Box 465, Folder 7)
      - Was Khallid Abdul Muhamad Assassinated?, 2004-01-12 (Box 465, Folder 8)
      - Who Brought the Slaves to America?, Undated (Box 467, Folder 16)
        2 copies
      - Who Killed this Believer?, Undated (Box 467, Folder 17)
      - Who Was Really Behind the Assassination of Malcolm X?, 1990-1992; Felder, Jack (Box 465, Folder 9)
      - You Come to Power Only When You Come to a Point, 2000-2003; Epps, S. (Box 466, Folder 17)
      - The Zodiac Constitution, Undated; Bey, C.M. (Box 466, Folder 18)
      - The Zulus, 1989-1999; Knight, Ian and Angus McBride (Box 465, Folder 10)
    - Health, Wellness, and Nutrition, 1955-2005
      - AIDS: Made in the USA, Undated; Miles, Zears L., Jr. (Box 468, Folder 1)
      - AIDS: Made in the USA Pt. 2, Undated; Miles, Zears L., Jr. (Box 468, Folder 2)
      - The Amazing to Modern Useful Plant Aloe Vera, Undated; Health Research Books (Box 470, Folder 4)
      - Amazing IBS Breakthroughs: Natural Remedies and Medical Miracles that Really Work, 2003; FC&A Medical Publishing (Box 468, Folder 3)
      - Anthrax Smallpox, 2001 (Box 468, Folder 4)
      - Asthma, Catarrh, Hay Fever & Sinusitis, Undated; Health Research Books (Box 468, Folder 5)
      - The Aura and What It Means to You, Undated (Box 468, Folder 6)
      - Auto-Urine Therapy, Undated (Box 470, Folder 6)
      - Be Your Own Doctor with Magnet Therapy, Undated (Box 470, Folder 8)
      - Beat High Blood Pressure Naturally, 2004 (Box 470, Folder 7)
      - Black Seed - A Cure for Every Disease but Death, 1999 (Box 470, Folder 9)
      - The Book of Sufi Healing, Undated; Chisti, Shayk Hakim Moinuddin (Box 470, Folder 3)
      - Cancer: Causes, Prevention, & Treatment: The Total Approach, Undated; Airola, Paavo (Box 470, Folder 10)
      - Catalog of Gaia Herbs Products, 2003-04; Center for Natural Healing (Box 468, Folder 3)
      - Crusador, 2003-06; Crusador Enterprises (Box 512, Folder 19)
      - The Crystal and Mineral Guide, Undated; Lee, John (Box 470, Folder 11)
      - Cure Arthritis Pain Naturally, 2004 (Box 470, Folder 12)
      - Doctors 100 All-Time Greatest Home Remedies, 1999 (Box 470, Folder 14)
      - The Doctor's Complete Booklet of Unbiased Breakthroughs, 2005 (Box 470, Folder 13)
      - Don't Drink the Water: The Essential Guide to Our Contaminated Drinking Water and What You Can Do About It, 1996; A'o, Lono Kahuna Kupua (Box 470, Folder 15)
      - Exotic Supplements, 1996; Canning, Peggy (Box 470, Folder 16)
      - The Facts of Nutrition, Undated; Hotema, Hilton; Health Research Books (Box 468, Folder 8)
      - Fat Blocker Foods, 2000 (Box 470, Folder 17)
      - The First Aid Handbook, 1997 (Box 471, Folder 1)
      - Flaxseed (Linseed) Oil and the Power of Omega-3, 1990 (Box 471, Folder 2)
      - Flaxseed and Wheat Germ - A Dynamic Duo, 2002; Donsbach, Kurt W. (Box 471, Folder 3)
      - Food: It's About Survival, Undated (Box 469, Folder 1)
      - Ginkgo Biloba: The amazing 200 million-year-old healer, 1993; Murray, Frank (Box 471, Folder 4)
      - Global Herb Manual, 1995; Fortisevn, Zeke (Box 471, Folder 5)
      - H.H. Tulku Buddha Maitreya's Metatronic Geometric Healing Tools, Undated (Box 471, Folder 7)
      - Hawaiian Noni, 1998; Elkins, Rita (Box 471, Folder 6)
      - Health Research Books, 2001 (Box 469, Folder 2)
      - Hemp Line Journal, Vol. 1, Issue 2, Undated (Box 512, Folder 20)
      - Hemp Line Journal/Marijuana: The Healing Herb - Family Council on Drug Awareness, Undated (Box 469, Folder 3)
      - The Herb Tea Book by Dorothy Hall, 1981; Hall, Dorothy (Box 471, Folder 12)
      - Hydrogen Peroxide & Ozone, 2004 (Box 471, Folder 9)
      - In The Fight for Prostate Health: New Discoveries have Surgery on the Ropes, 2000 (Box 469, Folder 4)
      - The International School of Orthopathy - Shelton & Clements, Undated; Health Research Books (Box 469, Folder 8)
      - Is Cancer Curable? Various Opinions, Suggestions & Diets Both Orthodox and Unorthodox, Undated; Health Research Books (Box 471, Folder 10)
      - Juice Fasting, 1991; Airola, Paavo (Box 471, Folder 8)
      - Life-Saving Health Secrets, 2000; DeSpain, J.J. (Box 471, Folder 11)
      - The Magic Temple, 1967; Hotema, Hilton; Health Research Books (Box 469, Folder 5)
      - Man's Higher Consciousness - Hilton Hotema, 1962; Hotema, Hilton (Box 469, Folder 6)
      - Metaphysical Healing, 1932, 1974; Raleigh, A.S.; Health Research Books (Box 469, Folder 7)
      - Mother Nature's Miracle Cures, 2003 (Box 471, Folder 13)
      - MSM: On Our Way Back to Health with Sulfur, 1998; Ley, Beth M. (Box 471, Folder 14)
      - Optimizing Health Through Nutrition, 1988; Amen, Ra Un Nefer (Box 486, Folder 23)
        Volume 2 Issue 3
      - Overcoming Asthma, Undated; Snodgrass, Beth (Box 471, Folder 15)
      - Pau d'Arco, 1977; Elkins, Rita (Box 470, Folder 5)
      - Recipes from the Herbal Kitchen, 2000 (Box 471, Folder 16)
      - Retirement Secrets - What They Don't Want You to Know by Bottom Line Secrets, Undated (Box 469, Folder 9)
      - The Revolt Against Chemicals, 1955; Bernard, Raymond (Box 469, Folder 10)
      - The Sacred Principles of Health, Undated; Valentine, Phillip (Box 469, Folder 11)
      - The Secret of Regeneration, 1963; Hotema, Hilton (Box 470, Folder 1)
      - Sexual Energy: Sexual Wisdom Now and in the 21st Century, 1992; Pookrum, Jewel (Box 470, Folder 2)
      - St. John's Wort - Nature's Antidepressant, 1997; Hawken, C.M. (Box 471, Folder 17)
      - Vaccines are Dangerous: A Warning to the Black Community, 1991; Cost, Curtis (Box 471, Folder 18)
      - The Way to Happiness: A Common Sense Guide to Better Living, 1989 (Box 471, Folder 19)
      - What everyone should know about depression, 1995 (Box 471, Folder 20)
      - The Zodiac and the Salts of Salvation, Undated; Bey, R.V. (Box 471, Folder 21)
    - Legal and Financial, 1992-2004
      - Asset Protection: How to Legally Become Lawsuit Proof!, Undated (Box 472, Folder 3)
      - Citizens Rule Book, Undated (Box 512, Folder 18)
      - Credit Emergency Surgery by Bernard Muhammad, Muhammad, Bernard (Box 472, Folder 10)
      - Discounts! Discounts! And More Discounts! -, 1999 (Box 475, Folder 1)
      - How to Bear-Proof Your Portfolio - Bottom Line Secrets, 2004 (Box 475, Folder 3)
      - How to Buy Real Estate When You're Broke & Bankrupt, 1996; Muhammad, Dexter (Box 475, Folder 4)
      - How to Save 100% On Your Income Tax, 1992; Martin, Len (Box 475, Folder 5)
      - The Income Tax Is Voluntary!, Undated; Gerstad, Heidi L. (Box 472, Folder 1)
      - Liberty Action Pack, 1993 (Box 472, Folder 6)
      - The Liberty Library, 1993 (Box 472, Folder 4)
      - The Liberty Library II, 1993 (Box 472, Folder 5)
      - Lowering Your Profile: How to Legally Establish Nevada Residency, 1993 (Box 472, Folder 7)
      - Moorish Civic Services, Undated (Box 475, Folder 2)
      - Redemption in Law: Theory and Practice - "Cracking the Code", Undated (Box 472, Folder 2)
      - The Tax That Never Was: The IRS & The Federal Income Tax, 1993 (Box 472, Folder 8)
      - Triple Your Money Fast! Insiders Pick the Next Hot Sectors in the Stock Market - Bottom Line Secrets, 2004 (Box 475, Folder 6)
      - Uniform Commercial Code, Undated (Box 472, Folder 9)
      - The Ultimate Tax-Free Estate Plan - Bottom Line Secrets, 2004 (Box 475, Folder 7)
    - Occult, Paranormal, and Secret Societies, 1960-1999
      - A Manual of Occultism by, Undated; Sepharial; Health Research Books (Box 476, Folder 9)
      - Agharta - The Subterranean World, 1960; Bernard, Raymond; Health Research Books (Box 475, Folder 8)
      - The Alchemist, 1996-1997 (Box 475, Folder 9)
        Volumes 1.1-1.2
      - Aliens - Encounters with the Unexplained, 1997; Day, Marcus (Box 475, Folder 10)
      - Atlantis and Lemuria, Undated; Steiner, Rudolf; Health Research Books (Box 476, Folder 10)
      - The Conspiracy Summit, 1999 (Box 475, Folder 11)
      - The Controllers: The Hidden Rulers of Earth Identified by Commander X, 1994; Commander X (Box 475, Folder 12)
      - The Cult of the All-Seeing Eye, 1964; Spenser, Robert Keith (Box 475, Folder 13)
      - Defending Sacred Ground: The Andromedan Compendium, 1997; Valerian, Valdamar (Box 475, Folder 14)
      - Everything You Wanted to Know About Sedona in a Nutshell, 1998; Dongo, Tom (Box 477, Folder 2)
      - The Fate of Colonel Fawcett, Undated; Cummins, Geraldine; Health Research Books (Box 476, Folder 11)
      - Flying Saucers from the Earth's Interior, Undated; Bernard, Raymond; Health Research Books (Box 475, Folder 15)
      - The Genesis and History of the Cosmic Conflict, 1995 (Box 475, Folder 16)
      - The Hollow Earth, 1964; Bernard, Raymond; Health Research Books (Box 476, Folder 1)
      - Invisibility & Levitation: How-To Keys to Personal Performance, 1998; Commander X (Box 476, Folder 2)
      - The Leading Edge - Leading Edge International Research Journal Issues 104 & 110, 1998 (Box 476, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous Magazine Excerpts, 1977-2003 (Box 476, Folder 8)
      - Oracles of Nostradamus, Undated; Ward, Chas A.; Health Research Books (Box 477, Folder 1)
      - Telepathy the Ancient Science, Undated (Box 476, Folder 6)
      - Tesla: Man of Mystery, 1992; X, Michael (Box 477, Folder 3)
      - The Occult Technology of Power, 1974; Hemmitt, Bobby (Box 476, Folder 4)
      - The Talisman of the United States, Undated; Westbrook, Charles L., Jr. (Box 476, Folder 5)
      - Women's Masonry, or Masonry by Adoption: The Complete Text of the Oldest Masonic Ritual Written for Women, Dated 1765, Undated (Box 476, Folder 7)
    - Religion, 1959-2006
      - 1990 A.D. What Our Savior Teaches and What We Ansaarullah Live By, 1990 (Box 473, Folder 1)
      - 20 Reasons to Abandon Christianity, 2000; Bufe, Chaz; See Sharp Press (Box 473, Folder 2)
        Tucson, AZ
      - A History of Satanism, 1997; McCabe, Joseph; See Sharp Press (Box 474, Folder 3)
      - A Mansion is Built for You in Paradise, 1986; Fitch, Theodore; Health Research (Box 474, Folder 9)
      - Agharta, Undated; Dickhoff, Robert Ernst (Box 473, Folder 3)
      - Al-Jihadul Akbar, 1974-04; Ikhwanul Muslimoon, Inc. (Box 546, Folder 2)
      - Al-Qur'an: The Miracle of Miracles, Undated; Deedat, Ahmed (Box 479, Folder 9)
      - Altered Images, 1999-2002; Khu, Khepera Sahu; A&B Publishers Group (Box 473, Folder 4)
        Brooklyn, NY
      - The Ansaru Allah Community, Undated; Haddad, Yvonne Yazbeck and Jane Idleman Smith (Box 473, Folder 5)
      - Arabs and Israel: Conflict or Conciliation?, 1989-07; Deedat, Ahmed (Box 473, Folder 6)
      - The Astral World: Its Scenes, Dwellers and Phenomena, Undated; Panchadasi, Swami (Box 473, Folder 7)
      - The Astral World: Its Scenes, Dwellers and Phenomena, Undated; Panchadasi, Swami (Box 481, Folder 3)
      - The Black Presence in the Lands of the Bible, 1990; Watts, Daud Malik (Box 478, Folder 13)
      - The Breath of Life and The Flame Divine, Undated; Hotema, Hilton (Box 478, Folder 14)
      - Chicago Scene Vol. 10, No. 17, 1995-09-25-1995-10-17 (Box 478, Folder 15)
      - Christian-Muslim Dialogue, 1984; Baagil, H.M. (Box 473, Folder 8)
      - The Circle of Life: "Clock of Destiny", Undated; Bey, C.M. (Box 473, Folder 9)
      - Clock of Destiny Volume 1, 1973; Bey, C.M. (Box 473, Folder 10)
      - The Cosmic Conflict, Undated (Box 478, Folder 19)
      - The Cosmic Family Volume 1, 1993-1995; Gabriel of Sedona; The Extension School of Melchizedek Publishing (Box 473, Folder 11)
        West Sedona, AZ
      - Creation: Cosmic Radiation, 1962; Hotema, Hilton (Box 478, Folder 16)
      - Crescent Books-Clothing Supplies Catalog, 1988 (Box 473, Folder 12)
      - Desert Storm: Has It Ended?, Undated; Deedat, Ahmed (Box 479, Folder 10)
      - The Divine Sayings of the Honorable Elijah Muhammad, 2002; Secretarius MEMPS Publications (Box 473, Folder 14)
        Atlanta, GA
      - Does God Exist? 12 Proofs of the Nonexistence of God, Undated; Faure, Sebastien; See Sharp Press (Box 473, Folder 13)
      - Don't You Ever Blame the Hon. Elijah Muhammad Again, 1987; Saud, King (Box 473, Folder 15)
      - Egyptian Mysteries Vol. 1, 2004; Ashby, Sebai Muata (Box 478, Folder 17)
      - The Egyptian Philosophers: Ancient African Voices from Imhotep to Akhenaten, 2000; Asante, Molefi Kete (Box 473, Folder 16)
      - Egyptian Yoga: Movements of the Gods and Goddesses, 1996-2001; Ashby, Muata and Karen "Dja" Ashby (Box 478, Folder 18)
      - Eshu-Eleggua-Elegbara: Santería and the Orisha of the Crossroads, 2000; Canizares, Baba Raul; Original Publications (Box 473, Folder 17)
        Plainview, NY
      - The Fake Sunni Muslim Religion is the Anti-Christ, Undated; The Original Tents of Kedar (Box 473, Folder 18)
      - First Steps in Egyptian, Undated; Budge, E.A. Wallis; Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co. (Box 473, Folder 19)
        London
      - The Flag of Islam, 1974; Muhammad, Elijah (Box 474, Folder 1)
        Chicago, IL
      - The Great Law, 1962; Hotema, Hilton (Box 479, Folder 1)
      - The Great Pyramid of Egypt, Undated; Ford, S.H. (Box 474, Folder 2)
      - The Great Red Dragon, Undated; Hotema, Hilton (Box 479, Folder 2)
      - History & Catechism of the Moorish Orthodox Church of America, 1986-1992; Selim, Ustad and Arif Hussein Al-Camaysar; Crescent Moon Press (Box 474, Folder 4)
      - Holy Fahamme Gospel or Divine Understanding, Undated; Johnson, Paul; Fahamme Temples of Islam and Culture (Box 479, Folder 3)
      - How Rushdie Fooled the West, Undated; Deedat, Ahmed (Box 479, Folder 8)
      - The Human Aura: Astral Colors and Thought Forms, Undated; Panchadasi, Swami; Yoga Publication Society (Box 474, Folder 5)
      - The Importance of the Prohibition of Riba in Islam, 1996; Hosein, Imran N.; Masjid Darul Qur'an (Box 474, Folder 6)
        Long Island, NY
      - Initiation into Egyptian Yoga and Neferian Spirituality, 1996-2002; Ashby, Muata Abhaya (Box 481, Folder 6)
      - Is the Bible God's Word?, Undated; Deedat, Ahmed (Box 474, Folder 7)
      - Is There Eternal Life After Death?, Undated; York-El, Malachi Z. (Box 474, Folder 8)
      - Islam for Latinos, Undated (Box 512, Folder 16)
      - Kingdom of Heaven, Undated; Hotema, Hilton (Box 481, Folder 7)
      - Land of Light, Undated; Hotema, Hilton (Box 481, Folder 8)
      - Let the Bible Speak, Undated; Muhsin, Ali (Box 481, Folder 1)
      - Living Fire or God's Law of Life, Undated; Hotema, Hilton (Box 481, Folder 9)
      - Love and Light, Undated; Rashid, A.A. (Box 481, Folder 10)
      - Man's Higher Consciousness (copy 1), Undated; Hotema, Hilton (Box 481, Folder 11)
      - Man's Higher Consciousness (copy 2), Undated; Hotema, Hilton (Box 481, Folder 12)
      - Matrix II, 1990-1991; Valerian, Valdamar (Box 484)
      - Matrix III Vol. 2, 1995; Valerian, Valdamar (Box 483)
      - Matrix Pt. III (1/2), Undated (Box 479, Folder 4)
      - Matrix Pt. III (2/2), Undated (Box 479, Folder 5)
      - Matrix V, 2001; Valerian, Val (Box 483)
      - May the Farce be with You: A lighthearted look at why God does not exist, 2001; Pedersen, April; See Sharp Press (Box 474, Folder 10)
      - Melchizedek and the Mystery of Fire, 1996; Hall, Manly P. (Box 481, Folder 5)
      - Metu Neter Oracle Interpretation, 1997; Amen, Ra Un Nefer (Box 483, Folder 1)
      - Miracle of the Ages: The Great Pyramid of Gizeh, Undated; Smith, Worth (Box 474, Folder 11)
      - Moorish Guidepost Vol. 1, Issue 1, 2005 (Box 479, Folder 6)
      - Moorish Guidepost Vol. 1, Issue 2, 2006 (Box 479, Folder 7)
      - Muhammed the Greatest, Undated; Deedat, Ahmed (Box 479, Folder 11)
      - Muhammed the Greatest, Undated; Deedat, Ahmed (Box 474, Folder 12)
      - Muhammed: The Natural Successor to Christ, Undated; Deedat, Ahmed (Box 479, Folder 12)
      - The Muslim Green Pages, 1984 (Box 483, Folder 2)
      - Muslim-Christian Dialogue, 1984; Baagil, H.M. (Box 474, Folder 13)
      - Muslim-Christian Dialogue, Undated; Baagil, H.M. (Box 481, Folder 4)
      - Mysteries of Isis, 1996-2002; Ashby, Muata (Box 483, Folder 3)
      - Nuwaupic: The Ancient Egyptian Mystery Language, Undated (Box 474, Folder 14)
      - Obatala: Santería and the White Robed King of the Orisha, 2000; Canizares, Baba Raul; Original Publications (Box 474, Folder 15)
      - The Oracle, 2005; Bey, C.M. (Box 474, Folder 16)
      - The Origin and Evolution of Freemasonry Connected with the Origin and Evolution of the Human Race, 1985; Churchward, Albert; George Allen & Unwin LTD (Box 484, Folder 1)
      - Philadelphia Uncovered, 2006; Muhammad, Ali (Box 484, Folder 2)
      - The Primal Power in Man or The Kundalini Shakti, 1971; Narayanananda, Swami (Box 484, Folder 3)
      - The Prohibition of Riba in the Qur'an and Sunnah, 1997; Hosein, Imran N.; Masjid Darul Qur'an (Box 478, Folder 1)
      - The Rosicrucians: Their Rites and Mysteries, Undated; Jennings, Hargrave; Chatto and Windus (Box 484)
      - Sacred Biography and History (Part 1), Undated; Tiffany, Osmond (Box 485)
      - Sacred Biography and History (Part 2), Undated; Tiffany, Osmond (Box 485)
      - Sacred Geometry, 1997-1998; Melchizedek, Drunvalo (Box 484)
      - Sacred Wisdom of the Ancients: Living Fire and God's Law of Life, 1959 (Box 485, Folder 3)
      - Salaam, 1960-07 (Box 478, Folder 2)
      - Salah: The Muslim Prayer, Undated (Box 478, Folder 3)
      - The Satanic Bible, 1969; LaVey, Anton Szandor; Avon Books (Box 485, Folder 7)
        New York, NY
      - Selected References to the Eye of Heru from the Coffin Texts, 1990-1998; King, Richard D. (Box 485, Folder 5)
      - The Serpent Power, 1996-2003; Ashby, Sebai Muata (Box 485, Folder 6)
      - Shango: Santería and the Orisha of Thunder, 2000; Canizares, Baba Raul; Original Publications (Box 478, Folder 4)
      - The Smoky God and other Inner Earth Mysteries, 1993; Beckley, Timothy Green; Inner Light Publications (Box 478, Folder 5)
      - The Soul in Egyptian Metaphysics & The Book of the Dead, 1997; Hall, Manly P.; Philosophical Research Society (Box 478, Folder 6)
      - The Talmud Unmasked: The Secret Rabbinical Teachings Concerning Christians, Undated; Pranaitis, I.B. (Box 478, Folder 7)
        St. Petersburg
      - Thamaniya: The Most Ancient Cosmological Doctrine, Undated; International Society of Indigenous Sovereigns (Box 512, Folder 17)
      - The Titans: Gnostic Mythology, Undated; Hemmit, Bobby (Box 485, Folder 1)
      - To Whom It May Concern (Arabs): Is A Green Card More Valuable than Obedience to Allah???, Undated (Box 478, Folder 8)
      - Truth, Falsehood, 1986; Muhammad, W. Deen (Box 485, Folder 4)
      - Tut-Ankh-Amen: The Living Image of the Lord, 1997; Gadalla, Moustafa; Bastet Publishing (Box 478, Folder 9)
        Erie, PA
      - What Every American Should Know about Islam & the Muslims, 1985-12; Nu'Man, Muhammad Armiya (Box 481, Folder 2)
      - Who Killed this Believer?, Undated (Box 478, Folder 10)
      - Why Astrology?, Undated (Box 478, Folder 11)
      - You and the Sons of the Green Light, Undated (Box 485, Folder 2)
      - Zodiacal View on You--Vol. 2, Psychology of Astrology, Undated; Bey, R.V. (Box 478, Folder 12)
    - Dwight York and the Nuwaubian Nation, 1992-2001
      Arranged by publisher.
      - Tents of Abraham, 1992-1993 (Box 492, Folder 1)
        Editions 1, 8, 9, 11, 14
      - International Supreme Council of Shriners, 2001 (Box 492, Folder 2)
      - Tama-Re, Undated (Box 492, Folder 3)
        No. 171
      - Ancient Egyptian Order, Undated (Box 492, Folder 4)
        Nos. 1, 2, 3
      - Ancient Egyptian Order, 1999-2000 (Box 492, Folder 5)
        Ed. 1, Vol. 3, 4, 6; Ed. 2, Vol. 1; Ed. 5, Vol. 1
      - The Egiptian Church of Karast "Christ" Inc., Undated (Box 492, Folder 6)